I can't believe he broke up with me
Who? Peter?
Yeah Peter
What did he do?
Okay. To be fair, I saw it coming
But I thought I would be the one to
break up with him first, you know?
Oh nooo
So like okay but like he never smiled at me
He doesn't even smile?
He doesn't smile and like he always gets salads.
He's obsessed with salads
EW who eats vegetables?
Yeah like every time we went out to eat,
he would always get himself a salad
Gross...
And he would never buy me food
Like he even went to Taiwan for my birthday
What the heck?
Isn't that so ridiculous? So ridiculous...
Anyways, ugh, I'm SO PISSED
What happened?
It's a really long story
You know what? He sucks
I think you should just
find another boyfriend
Peter doesn't deserve you
Um, I don't want another boyfriend
I'm so over this boyfriend thing
No, I'm serious. You should
find someone else that's better
Do it for me?
No
Why not?
Cause I just got off of a
relationship with Peter
Well, Peter is terrible. Just find
someone else that's better than him
You know what? You're right.
He doesn't deserve all this
Like, come on
Yeah
Alright.
We should find you a new boyfriend.
How are we going to do that?
We can use Tinder
Eh, nah
mmm - mm
Wait, isn't that the guy that
just opened the door for us?
I saw him just now
I don't remember
Dude, he's really cute
I mean, he's okay, but I-
No no no, trust me, he's
even better in person
I think you should go
on a date with him
Yvonne: Okay I'm going to swipe right
Vivian: You should swipe right
Okay, I'm going to swipe right, but like-
Wait wait wait, also message him your
number so he can contact you
Wait no, why?
No, so he can reach out to you first
Trust me, just do it this time
Wh- oh-okay...
[loud knocking]
Woah woah woah
Hi-
Wooahh
Ankit: Hey Michelle
Michelle: I'm back baby
Michelle: Kiss me. Kiss me!
Ankit: No no no, no no no no
Michelle: Kiss me- please
Ankit: No no no no no
Michelle: Why won't you kiss me?
Ankit: No no no- woah
Alright, come on. Let's put you
in bed. Let's put you in bed
Let's go. Come on. Alright
Give me your hand
Alright, let's go. Come on.
Alright here. Okay, you good?
Michelle: Why won't you kiss me?
We’re broken up. We can’t do this-
We can’t do this. I’m sorry.
We’re broken up.
Just take care of me for tonight
All right. I’ll take care of you.
Here. Lay down. Lay down.
Here’s a pillow.
And here. Have Scruffy.
He’ll take care of you okay?
I’m going to get you some water, okay?
Finally.
Oh. I got matched with Yvonne.
Maybe I should take her to dinner
Ankit: Hey! You’re Yvonne right?
Yvonne: Yes…
Ankit: Hi I’m Ankit
Yvonne: Hi
Ankit: I got this for you
Uh because I’m from Africa
And we don’t have Christmas there
Yvonne: Oh wow
Ankit: Santa doesn’t have time to get-
to our part of the world.
Oh thank you so much
And uh I also got you this
I call him Scruffy. My mom
gave him to me.
And I really want you to have him
That’s so sweet of you. Aww
Uh do you want to go grab some coffee?
Yes, great!
Uh, so yeah back home in Africa
I actually compete on the
national high jump team
Do you want to see. It’s like super cool
I can jump super high
Ready, ready, alright 1, 2, 3
Woahh. That’s so cool!
I wish I was just like you
Super cool, huh- yeah
That’s me. Super cool.
Here wait wait, I’m going to do this
super cool thing right here.
[pants tearing]
Woahh
Skittt
Wait, are you okay?
Yeah
Ripped my pants
I’ll bet you that I can climb
that light pole
Yvonne: That light pole?
Ankit: Yeah that light pole, ready?
Ankit: On three…
Yvonne: Okay, 3 , 2 ,1
Yvonne: Oh wow
Ankit: Yeah
So uh that’s just some other
cool thing
Yeah no that is really cool
My bag is really heavy
Oh- oh skit here. Do you want me to
take your bag for you?
Yvonne: Yeah, yeah yeah
Ankit: Here I got that, okay
Yvonne: It's like not that heavy
Ankit: Got it, got it. It’s all good.
You know just.. working out
Doing my thing
(Oh my god)
Are you okay?
Oh, no totally solid- absolutely.
Yvonne: Okay, uh-huh. Alright
Ankit: Yeah no I'm good, I'm good
Yeah, so uh do you want
to have a seat?
So uh, I had a really fun time
with you today, you know
just like, doing fun stuff. And
I was wondering um-
if you wanted to be my girlfriend?
Yeah, I do actually. I had a
super fun time today as well.
Yeah. Of course you did.
Hey girl, you know what this
T-shirt's made of?
What?
Boyfriend material
Ooh. Is it true that the darker
the chocolate, the richer it is?
Ohh yeah.
Hey Alyssa, it's Ankit. Uh,
can we move our plans earlier?
Because I've got a meeting
later on tonight
Yeah, alright cool. See
you then. Bye.
Oh my god Vivian. The last two
days with Ankit have been soo nice.
He's such a sweetheart!
Aww, really?
Yeahh. Oh my god. You know
what you should do?
What?
You should like- give him
a hard time for me
So I can like see how he acts
under pressure for me, you know?
Vivan: I'll go see if he's a good guy
Yvonne: Yeah, exactly
And then I'll see if you
should actually date him
You know, Vivian, you're the most
beautiful girl I've ever seen
I know.
You know, Yvonne, you're the most
beautiful girl-
[Yvonne sneezes]
I'm sorry what was that?
You know, Alyssa, you're the most
beautiful girl I've ever seen
Oh Ankit you're so funny
You know, Michelle, you're the most
beautiful girl I've ever seen
[crazy laugh]
You know I've never liked
any girl the way I like you?
You know I've never liked any
other girl the way I like you?
Wait. Just don't touch me. Please.
Hey Ankit!
Hey... Yvonne. What-
how's it going?
Good. Are you still up for tonight?
Umm. Yeah, I'm a little busy, so
can I call you later?
Yvonne: Yeah.. sure.
Vivian: Wow..
Vivian: Who was that girl?
Yvonne: I have no idea,
but Ankit's supposed to be dating me
Wait, are you guys talking about Ankit?
Yeah, wait are we talking
about the same Ankit here?
Vivian and Michelle: Ankit Bhat??
Vivian: What?
Yvonne: Wait... hold on
What's going on?
He did the same exact thing to me!
Vivian: Wait what do you mean?
Yvonne: Wait, what did he do?
I have a lot to tell you guys
So, uh I had a really
fun time tonight
We should do this again sometime
Alyssa: Yeah we should
Ankit: Yeah? Alright, see ya
Night!
Alyssa! I need to talk to you!
[screams loudly]
Gas-ped! Are you serious?
Yeah. How could he date all of us at
the same time. That's so messed up.
Dude, we should get back at him.
But how?
I think I have a plan. Guys-
[whispers]
Yeah, hello?
Hello?
Hey what's up?
Hey babe
What's going on?
Do you want to come over
and have a drink with me?
Yeah, I'll be over in a bit.
Okay, see you
Ankit: Hey
Yvonne: Hey
Yvonne: How are you?
Ankit: Good
So I want to try something new today
Uh.. okay
Uh-huh. It's going to be really fun
Ankit: What is it?
Yvonne: Are you excited?
First we need to put this on you
Okay... Alright I'm excited
Here you go. There's the bed, alright.
Now...
Hey babe... What's taking so long?
I'm here, don't worry
Ohhh snap.
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry!
Too late!
No no no no no no no no
[wax strips being ripped off]